想要的话就进来啊
Uh, yeah, if you want too.
你要我进去吗
Do you want me too?
当然
Yeah, sure?
彼此彼此
So do I.
瑞秋  在一切还没开始之前
Okay Rach, before anything happens
有几个原则我想先说清楚
I just want to lay down a couple of ground rules.
今晚而已
This is just about tonight.
今晚过后
I don't to go through with this
你是你  我是我
if it's going to raise the question of "Us."
好吗  我希望这一切
Okay? I just want this to be
只是各取所需
about what it is!
罗斯  什么各取所需
And um, what-what is that Ross?
一夜情
The physical act of love.
什么  你疯了不成
What?! Are you crazy?
所以你刚才脱光光
Oh so-so you weren't trying to entice me
不是在勾引我吗
just now with your-your nakedness?
天啊  你看到了吗
Oh God, you saw me?!
你脱光光不是在勾引我
You weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness.
当然不是
Noo!! No!
你当真以为我想跟你上床吗
You thought, you actually thought I wanted to have sex with you?!
才不是呢
No!
不是
No! No!
不是不是
No-no-no-no.
等等我
Hey you guys wait!
这地方比伦敦好多了吧
Guys! This place is so much better than London! Okay?
有个打扮成埃及艳后的女士给了我一张优惠券
This lady dressed like Cleopatra gave me a coupon,
九毛九就能吃到牛排龙虾晚餐
99 cent steak and lobster dinner. Huh!
菲比  你又不吃肉
Phoebe, you don't eat animals.
只要九毛九  我连你都吃
For 99 cents, I'd eat you.
我完全可以耗在这里
Okay, I can totally settle down here.
我要的东西应有尽有
It's got everything I could ever want,
就连乔伊都在  你们看
including Joey! Look!
快看
Oh! Look! Hi!
天啊
Oh my God.
乔伊
Hey! Joey!
你的保险套真不赖
Love your condoms my man.
你们怎么在这里
What-what are you guys doing here?
不是要你们别来了
I thought I told you not to come.
你干嘛打扮成角斗士
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
因为我正在拍戏
Uhh, because I'm shooting a scene right now.
我扮演角斗士
Yeah, I uh, I play a gladiator.
你们等等
Uh, y'know what? Hold-hold on a second.
可以停吗
Can we cut?
我朋友来了  我要休息一下
Yeah, my-my friends are here, I'm gonna take a little break.
你是在跟谁说话
Who are you talking too?
导演啊  就是她
They uh director. Uhh, her.
好啦  这不是角斗士电影  我在这里工作
All right, all right, it's not a gladiator movie. I work here.
为什么  发生了什么事
Why?! What happened?!
那部电影因为没钱而停拍
Well, the movie got shutdown because they ran out of money,
我在这里工作  等电影重新开拍
so I'm working here 'til it starts up again,
如果真有这一天的话
if it ever does.
我真的很遗撼
I'm so sorry.
对不起  没跟你们说  抱歉
Look, I'm sorry I didn't tell ya.  I'm sorry man.
没关系  互相隐瞒
No-no, that's okay, apparently there's a new policy
显然成了新的规矩
where we don't have to share everything with everybody.
我就知道你听了心里会有疙瘩
I knew you were not okay with that.
你是角斗士耶
So you're a gladiator!
他们怎么了
Yeah, what-what's going on?
莫妮卡和理查德吃了午饭
Monica had lunch with Richard.
道森吗(演员)
Dawson?!
不是啦  要不然一定超酷的
Noo! But that would've been so cool!
是那个男朋友理查德
No! Her boyfriend Richard!
没任何意义  好吗
It meant nothing! Okay?
你怎么到现在还不相信我
After all this time, how can you not trust me?
你瞒着我跟大胡子帅哥吃午饭
When you go lunching with hunky moustache men
要我怎么相信你
and don't tell me about it!
你说的对  对不起  我早该跟你说的
You're right. I'm sorry. I should've told you.
谢谢
Thanks.
这样才对嘛
Aww, there we go.
我爱赌城
I love Vegas!
我保证下次一定会跟你说
I promise you, next time I will absolutely tell you.
下一次
Next time?
功亏一篑
Ooh, so close.
下不为例  你不能再跟他见面了
There's not gonna be a next time! You can not ever see him again!
我不能跟他见面  你不能对我发号施令
I can not see him? I mean, you can't tell me what to do!
有趣  刚才不就发了吗
That's so funny, because I think I just did!
如果你整晚都是这种态度
Oh y'know what? If you're gonna be acting like this all night,
我还是眼不见为净
I really, I don't even want to be around you.
我无所谓
Fine with me!
好  纪念日快乐
Fine! Happy Anniversary!
你们别这样嘛
Whoa! Whoa! Guys! Please! Come on! Come on!
这显然是个大误会
This is obviously just a big misunderstanding.
-才不是误会  -你在说什么
- No it is not! - What are you talking...
别看我  我只是在这里工作
Hey-hey don't look at me! I just work here!
罗斯
Okay umm, Ross?
我有点热  要脱毛衣
I'm-I'm really warm, so I'm going to be taking off my sweater.
我只是要你知道
Now, I'm just letting you know
这不是在勾引你一夜情
that this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.
对  真是太爆笑了
Yep! That's hilarious!
抱歉  我不闹了
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
昨晚你也很丢脸
Y'know, last night was embarrassing for you too.
不尽然啦
No, not really.
只是我没那么容易觉得丢脸
I just don't embarrass that easily.
什么  你根本就觉得非常丢脸
What?! You totally get embarrassed!
才没有  罗斯
No, I don't! Ross,
这是因为我比你更有安全感
I think I'm just a more secure person than you are.
是吗
Is that so?
是啊
Yeah.
小姐  不管你有多想要
Hey lady! I don't care how much you want it! Okay?!
我绝不会和你去厕所做爱
I am not gonna to have sex with you in the bathroom!
在古罗马时代  这不只是顶帽子而已
Hey, y'know in Roman times this was more than just a hat.
是吗
Really?
当然
Yeah, sure! Sure!
这可以用来刷地板
They would uh, they would scrub the floors with it!
抹去鞋子上的泥巴
They would use it to get the mud off their shoe.
有时候马肚子会弄脏
And sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty
-把这个戮进去就能...  -乔伊
- so they would stick it right... - Joey, I uh!
真不敢相信我的周年纪念日是这样过的
I can't believe this is how I'm spending my anniversary.
那我带你去个好地方
All right well, I'll take you someplace nice then.
今天有个人给我一百块的小费
Look! A guy tipped me a hundred bucks today.
他玩21点才一小时
Yeah-yeah, he was playing blackjack for like an hour
就赢了五千块  你相信吗  五千块
and he won $5,000. Can you believe that? $5,000!
如果我赢了五千  我就去加入健身房
Y'know, if I won $5,000 I'd join a gym,
把我的上半身练壮
y'know build up my upper body
再用棍子捅理查德的屁股
and hit Richard from behind with a stick!
等等  我何不效法那个人
Wait a minute! Why don't I do what that guy did?
把这一百变成五千
I'll take this $100 and turn it into $5,000!
五千再变成够拍电影的钱
And then I'll turn that into enough money
那电影就能重新开拍了
to get my movie going again!
祝你好运了
Good luck!
钱德勒  我不需要好运  我已经想透了
Chandler! I don't need luck. I have thought this through!
我懂了
I see.
不敢相信  今晚真是糟透了
I can't believe this! This is like the worst night ever!
莫妮卡  你和钱德勒的关系
Y'know Monica you had a minor setback
有了小小挫折
in your relationship with Chandler.
有什么大不了  不过是钱德勒罢了
Big deal! It's only Chandler.
我真的很遗憾
I am so sorry.
真离谱  我们吵架的理由太蠢了
This is crazy! I mean, it's such a stupid argument.
我根本不想再跟理查德见面了
I don't even wanna see Richard again.
那就去挽回啊  去找钱德勒
So go fix it! Go find Chandler!
他八成就待在你们的房间里
He's probably up in your room!
跟他说对不起  说你爱他
Tell him that you're sorry and that you love him.
菲比  你说的对  多谢你
Y'know what? You're right Phoebe. You're right. Thank you!
小意思
Sure!
好耶  赌城最棒
Yeah! Las Vegas, number one!
这是谁掉的吗
Anybody lose this?
下注吧
Comin' out. Place your bet.
下好离手
Dice are out.
一赔二  不还本
Double or nothin'! Pay the front line!
那个  我正好要去厕所
So uh, I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
好啦  继续走就是了
Yeah, all right. All right! Just keep walkin'! All right?
罗斯  你干嘛
Ross! What are you...
先生  对不起  他太喜欢你了
I'm sorry sir. I just, I think he just really likes you.
你知道那个和学生  生了孩子的老师吗
Hey! Y'know that teacher who had a baby with her student?
搞什么
What the? What...
小姐  需要我效劳吗
Miss? May I help you?
对  不好意思  你们有多的裤子吗
Yes, I'm sorry. Do you have any extra pants?
我朋友出了点小状况
Umm, my friend seems to have had a little accident.
可以换一百元筹码吗
Can I change a hundred?
换一百元筹码
Changing one hundred!
先生  祝您好运
Good luck sir.
全押了
Let's ride.
13点
13.
再来
Hit me!
要命
Ohh man!
慢着
Wait!
钱德勒  说了你一定不相信
Chandler! You are not gonna believe this!
我找到我的双胞手了
I have found my identical hand twin!
什么
What?
我的双胞手啊
My identical hand twin!
什么是双胞手
What's an identical hand twin?
钱德勒  太不可思议了
It was incredible! Chandler,
发牌员的手跟我一模一样
the dealer's hands were exactly like me!
就跟照镜子没两样
It-it was like looking at my hands in a mirror!
你确定不是在照镜子吗
Are you sure you weren't  looking at your hands in a mirror?
你不懂这件事的意义吗
Don't you see what this means?!
我大可忘了那部蠢电影
I can forget about that stupid movie.
我要变成百万富翁了
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
怎么变
How?
我还没有完全想出来
Look, I don't have it all worked out yet,
不过保证很有赚头
but it's gotta mean big money!
拜托  一模一样的手耶
Come on! Identical hands!
我得再问一次
Again I must go back to,
怎么赚
how?
这里可是赌城  大家就爱付钱看怪东西
This is Vegas man! People will pay to see freaky stuff!
你愿意付多少钱  看两次这只手
Okay, how much would you pay to see this hand twice?
乔伊  我说不出个价钱
Y'know, I-I can't really put a price on that Joe.
你又不支持我了
Hey, are you unsupporting me again?
不  我百分百支持你
No! No! I support you 100%!
只是我一时没回过神来
I just didn't, I didn't get it right away.
我现在懂了  双胞手
Y'know now I'm caught up! Identical hand twins!
这点子能值上一百万
It's a million-dollar idea!
菲比  我找到我的双胞手了
Pheebs!! I found my identical hand twin!
你真幸运
Ohh, you are so lucky!
莫妮卡呢  你们和好没
So, where's Monica? Did you guys make up?
没有
No!
可是她刚才上来了啊
But she just came up here!
那是乔伊
That was Joey!
怪了  那她去了哪里
I wonder where she is. That is so weird.
或许在跟理查德说话吧
Yeah, well, she's probably talking to Richard.
你有完没完
Would you stop that!
你知道她和理查德吃完中饭
Do you wanna know the first thing she said
回来后第一句话是什么吗
when she came back from her lunch with Richard?
她对他完全没感觉了  她爱的是你
She didn't feel anything for him. She loves you!
真的
Really?
是的  她很难过
Yes! Now, she feels terrible!
她真的很想跟你和好  你一定得找到她
She really wants to make up! You gotta find her.
好
Okay.
很好
Good.
我真应该开始戴帽子了
I should really start wearing hats!
欢迎来到赌城
Welcome to Las Vegas.
谢谢  一路还愉快吗
Thank you! Enjoy your flight?
很开心  谢谢  非常棒
Yes, I did. Thank you very much, it was excellent.
希望您一路还愉快
Hope you had a nice flight.
太愉快了
Ohh, it was the best!
登记台应该在那里
I think the check in is that way.
小孩子最喜欢我了
Ohh, kids love me.
菲比
Phoebe!
你们来了
You guys are here! Yay!
你去参加化妆舞会了吗
What? Did you go to a costume party?
我来猜  你是扮潘乔·维拉(墨西哥革命领袖)
Let me guess umm Pancho Vila?
你是鲍勃·萨吉特(演员)
and you're Bob Saget.
潘乔·维拉
Pancho Vila?
是啊
Yeah!
菲比  你在说什么啊  我没有...
What are you talking about Pheebs?  I don't...
天啊  你在我脸上乱画
Oh my God, you drew on me?!
谁叫你弄湿我裤子
Hey, you wet my pants!
这是哪门子派对啊
Whoa, what kind of party was this?
罗斯  我打从下飞机就是这样子
Ross, I have been walking around like this since the plane!
你实在是太过分了
I can-you have so crossed a line.
瑞秋  等等  男厕在那里
Rach! Wait! The men's room is that way.
怎么了
What?
那女士接我的机子玩就赢钱
That's like the third time that lady's
这已经是第三次了
won on a machine I was playing.
我赌她一定是那种人
Oooohhh, I'll bet she's one of those people.
间谍吗
M-M-Mole people?
不是啦  是跟赌人
What? No-no, a lurker.
跟赌人是什么
Oh. What's a lurker?
你玩赌博机  没有赢钱
Okay when you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out,
跟赌人等你放弃就来接手玩  然后
a lurker waits for you to give up and then...
杀你灭口
Kills you?
不  他们半路杀进来偷走本来你会中的大奖
No. They swoop in and steal your jackpot.
你怎么会知道这种事
How do you know about this?
我奶奶以前就干这行
My nana used to do it.
她就是这样帮我付舞蹈...空手道学费的
That's how she paid for all my dance-karate lessons.
舞蹈空手道
Dance karate?
对  那是种美丽却致命的运动
Yes, it's a deadly but beautiful sport.
我弄不掉
All right, it won't come off!
什么
What?!
我弄不掉
It won't come off!
天啊  瑞秋  你确定吗
Oh my God! Rach-Rach, are-are-are you sure?
不确定  其实我弄掉了又自己再画回去
No, actually I took it off then I drew it back on.
你们到了
Hey-hey-hey you made it!
乔伊
Joey!!
你朋友是谁  他好正点
Who's your friend? He's hot!
多谢你了
Thanks man.
钱德勒跟我说过了  电影的事我很遗撼
Hey listen I uh, talked to Chandler, sorry about the movie.
不用遗憾  不要也罢
No, don't be sorry. I don't need it anymore.
我找到了我的双胞手
I found my identical hand twin!
你的什么
Your what?
我的双胞手
My identical hand twin!
那个人的手跟我的完全一样
The person whose hands are exactly like mine!
这可是金矿
This thing is a gold mine!
什么
What?!
靠那个赚不了钱的
That's not gonna make you any money!
好  你这样想也无所谓
Okay. Well, if that's how you feel about it, fine!
到时我盖了手形的豪宅  你们谁都别想来住
None of you get to live with me in my great big hand-shaped mansion!
菲比你除外  大拇指给你住
Except uh, you Pheebs. You can live in the thumb.
来吧  加油
All right baby, come on!
漂亮  势不可挡
Yes! Yes! I am on fire!
莫妮卡  再见
See you later Mon.
等等  钱德勒  你在干嘛
Wait Chandler, what are you doing?!
你看呢  我要回家
What does it look like? I'm going home.
等等  为什么
What? Wait! Why?
钱德勒  钱德勒  你等等
Chandler! Chandler! Wait!
对不起  我只是玩了一下
I'm sorry, I was just playing for one second!
我本来打算要跟你说
I was trying to find you to tell you that,
你不让我再见理查德  我答应
look if you don't want me to see Richard again, I won't!
他对我没有任何意义
He means nothing to me!
得了吧  我又不是瞎子
Come on! I was there!
我知道他是你追求的真爱
I know he's the love of your life.
现在不是了
Not any more.
真的
Really?!
Really!
忘了什么要回家的事
All right? Let's forget about this going home stuff
我们来庆祝周年纪念吧
and celebrate our anniversary.
包里是空的
Okay, this is empty.
我想搞得煽情些  可是我又讨厌打包
Yeah, I wanted to make a dramatic scene, but I hate packing.
另一个人呢
Uhh, hey. Where's the other guy?
哪个人
Which guy?
高高的  深色头发
He's kinda tall, dark hair,
手跟我的一模一样  你看
hand looks exactly like this. See?
我不知道什么手
I don't know about the hands,
不过在我之前的发牌员  刚去上厕所了
but the guy that was here before me just went to the bathroom.
知道了
Okay.
你好吗
How you doin'?
我很忙
Very busy.
对耶  好吧
Right! Okay.
你好  我有个问题
Yes, hello. I have a question.
我用你们的笔  画了我朋友的脸
Umm, I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
下巴上一撮再加两撇山羊胡
A beard and a moustache.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不  她不这么想
No, she didn't think so.
对啊  就像...总之
I know it's like anyway, umm
用化妆品盖不过去  我们试过所有方法
well make-up didn't cover it and we've tried everything to get it off
都去不掉  该怎么办
and nothing's worked. What-what do we do?
好的  是
Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah.
好的  多谢
Oh! Okay. Okay, thank you!
擦不掉的
Yeah, it's not coming off.
什么  那他还说了什么
What?! What else did he say?
他说他觉得我很逗
Umm, he said he thought I was funny. So...
好了  听我说  我们下楼
Okay, look-look umm, let's just go downstairs,
去好好玩  你就会忘记这回事了
we'll have some fun, and you will forget all about it.
休想  罗斯  我这个样子绝对不出房门
Ross, no! There is no way I am leaving this room looking like this!
别这样啦  瑞秋  没有那么难看
Oh, come on! Rach, it's-it's not that bad.
罗斯  我变成人体涂鸦了
Ross, I am a human doodle!!
别因为一个白痴在你脸上乱画
Look, just because some idiot drew on your face
而剥夺你玩乐的权利
doesn't mean you shouldn't have any fun! Okay?
而且又没人会看你
And besides, hey-hey-hey no one is even gonna look at you. Okay?
这里可是赌城  怪人一大堆
This is Vegas! Hello! There are tons of other freaks here!
这里有一大堆怪人
There are tons...of...freaks here.
你不算
No other. No.
走啦  我保证没人会注意到
Come on! No one will notice, I swear!
好啦  是有一些人指指点点
Okay, there was some staring and pointing.
我得喝点酒
Okay, I need a, I need a drink!
冰箱里的酒都太贵了
Oh, hey y'know, they-they really overcharge you for that stuff.
但是谁在乎呢  我请客
But who cares?! Because it's all on me!
你的一点酒还真不少
That is, one big drink!
要吃澳洲坚果吗
Macadamia nut?
这个坚果还真值钱
Umm... Wow! That's-that's some pricey nut!
你真的很喜欢吃澳洲坚果呢
Really like those Macadamia nuts, huh?
不喜欢
Nope!
跟赌人  走开啦  快走
Get out of here you lurker! Go on! Get!
菲比
Hey Pheebs!
你们和好了
Ohh! You made up!
是啊  我没办法一直生他的气
Yeah, I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
没有钱钱的爱  她就不能活
Yeah, she couldn't live without the Chan Love.
去开房啦
Ohh, get a room.
我们有房间
We have one.
我知道  快去用啊
I know. Use it.
是啊  可得好好照顾你的手
That's right, you take good care of those babies!
你说什么
Excuse me?
我是乔伊啊
It's me, Joey!
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
乔伊啊
Joey!
秀手的那个
Oh-ho, yeah. Yeah, the hand guy.
我们要怎么处理双胞手的事
Okay, so what are we going to do about this hand twin thing?!
不用处理
Nothing?
你和我拥有上帝的赐礼
Look, you and I have been given a gift. Okay?
我们得好好利用  比如说手部模特
We have to do something with it. Like-like, hand modeling! Huh?
或是变魔术
Or-or magic!
太空总署一定也想找我们聊聊
And you know NASA's gonna wanna talk to us!
我得回去
I have to get back to...
等等  我们可以有自己的节目
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa-whoa! We could have our own show!
我们可以鼓掌  大家一定超爱看的
Y'know we could clap our hands together people will love it!
我还替咱们写了一首主题曲
Huh? And-and-and I wrote a song for us!
这是你的手
This hand is your hand!
这是我的手
This hand is my hand!
等等  那是你的手
Oh wait, that's your hand!
不对  是我的手
No wait, it's my hand!
还是算了
That's okay.
你还没听和声部分啊
But you haven't even heard the chorus!
天啊  我现在看起来好像我姑婆妙丽
Oh my God, I'm starting to look like my great aunt, Muriel.
你知道吗  其实我们用不着下楼
All right. Y'know what? We don't have to go downstairs!
房间里就可以是赌城
We can bring Vegas up to us!
快  我们来玩21点
All right, come on, come on, we'll play some blackjack.
开始  13点
Here we go. 13.
再加
Hit me!
23爆了
Oohh, 23.
我们这里的赌场23点最大
Which is what we play to at this casino!
你赢了十块钱
You win 10 dollars!
-我押了二十  -没错
- I bet 20. - Right!
帮我的小钱钱买双新鞋
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
好耶
Yes!
我这辈子还没看过有这么旺的
Yes! I've-I've never seen a roll like this in my life!
宝贝  你说对了  这次要多少
That's right baby! Okay, what do I want now?
好的  八  六
Okay, ah umm, ah, a 8. Ah, a 6?
选个数啦  你就这个任务
Pick a number! That is your only job!
-就八了  -多谢
- 8. 8! - Thank you!
这一把赢了  晚餐就请在场的各位吃牛排
If you get this one, we buy everybody here a steak dinner!
八
8!
我们不是真的要请他们吃牛排吧
We're not really gonna buy these people steak dinners are we?
-假的  -那就好
- Noo! - Okay, good!
这次掷多少
Okay, what do I want now?
试试双骰八
Ahh, ooh, try a hard 8.
什么
What?
四加四啦
Two fours.
好
Okay.
八
8!
千万要把握住她  你太幸运了
Don't you let her go! You're a lucky guy!
谢谢你  醉赌徒先生
Thank you, Mister Drunken Gambler!
如果这一把赢了
Okay, you get this and uh,
我们就租下这里最大的套房
we get the biggest suite in the place!
别激动  我说的我们是我和她
Wait-wait-wait-wait! We  get the biggest suite in the place.
好了  这里最大的套房  加油
All right, biggest suite in the place. Come on!
好耶  我爱你
Yes!! I love you!
我都忘记我们在吵什么了
I can't even remember what we were fighting about!
因为我和理查德吃中饭
Oh, that's because I had lunch with Rich-
我也忘了
Me neither!
这次要掷多少
Okay, what do I want now?
再来个双骰八
Another hard 8.
双骰八(也指困难)  叫简单八还差不多
Hard 8?! We should call it easy 8!
好了  这样吧
Okay, okay, I tell you what.
这次你掷出双骰八
You roll another hard eight;
我们今晚就在这里结婚
and we get married here tonight.
快掷啊
Go! Come on! Roll!
闭嘴
Shut up!!
好戏才正要上场
It just got interesting!
你刚才说什么
What did you just say?
你再掷一次双骰八
You roll another hard eight
我们今晚就在这里结婚
and we get married here tonight.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?!
是啊  我爱你
Yes! I love you!
我不曾这样爱过一个人
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
我也不曾这样爱过一个人
如果再掷八那就是天意
Okay, so if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign
我们就今晚结婚
and we do it!
你同意吗
What do you say?
好的
Okay.
双骰八
Hard eight.
有一个是四  另一个呢
Okay! That's a four! And where-where's the other one?
掉到桌子底下了
It went under the table.
统统不许动
Nobody move!
你找那边  我找这边
Okay, you look that way; I'll look this way!
好
All right!
在这里
Here it is! Here it is!
有可能是四  也有可能是五
That could be a four or a five.
你决定
It's your call.
是个四
It's a four.
我也这样觉得
I think so too.
算了  又没赢到钱
Oh well, lost again.
够了  我们去外面解决
That's it! You and me, outside!
我可不想看到你美丽的金发少一撮
I don't want to see you lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
假装没事
Be cool!
女士  你跟赌的日子结束了
Okay lady, your lurking days are over!
什么
What?!
从现在开始  我会抢先你一步跟赌
Yeah, from now on everyone you lurk, I'm gonna lurk first!
不管你找谁下手
You move on to someone else,
我都会捷足先登  一次都不放过
I'm gonna be one step ahead of you, every single time!
我每天都会时时紧紧跟着你
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day
直到星期一
'til Monday,
因为我那天要回家
because that's when I go home.
你何时要回家
When do you leave?
也是星期一
Also Monday.
几点  说不定能共乘计程车
What time? Maybe we can share a cab!
再加
Hit me.
我们得再去买牌
We need more cards.
对  还要再来点酒  等等
Yeah, and also we need more umm, drinks. Hold on a second.
没事
Whup, okay.
赌城吗
Hello! Vegas? Yeah,
我们还需要酒  对了
we would like some more alcohol, and y'know what else?
再来点啤酒
We would like some more beers.
我竟然忘了拨号
Hello? Ohh, I forgot to dial!
一定是酒和啤酒送来了
That must be our alcohol and beers!
是乔伊  我爱乔伊
Ohh, it's Joey! I love Joey!
我爱乔伊  乔伊跟一只鸭子住一起
Ohh, I love Joey! Joey lives with a duck!
你们听我说  我需要帮助
Look-look-look you guys, I need some help! Okay?
谁去叫我那个双胞手合作点
Someone is gonna help me convince my hand twin to cooperate!
我去  不管你有什么需要  找我就对了
I'll do it. Hey, whatever you need me to do, I'm your man.
你还好吗
Whoa-oh-whoa! Are you, are you okay?
对  我很好  谢了
Yeah! I'm fine! Thanks!
瑞秋  你好吗
Hey Rach, how you doin'?
宝贝  我很好  你呢
I'm doin' good, baby. How you doin'?
罗斯  别再让她喝了
Ross, don't let her drink anymore!
这是澳洲坚果
Ohh, here's that Macadamia nut!
不对  是别的东西
Nope! Something else.
好吧  你现在要干嘛
All right, so what do you want to do now?
我要离开这房间
I wanna get out of the room!
我真想念楼下
Y'know, I...I really miss downstairs.
要我离开这间房只有一个方法
Okay, y'know what? There's only one way I'm leaving this hotel room.
你好  我是罗斯
Well hello! I'm Ross!
祝你好运
Good luck to ya!
抱歉  先生  你脸上有东西
Excuse me sir, you've got a little something right here.
-你好  -你好
- Hello! - Hello!
我赢了  我赢了  我终于赢了
I won! I won! I finally won!
是我赢才对  那是我的硬币
I won! That was my quarter!
好啦  还给你  滚吧宝贝
Fine! Here! Take a hike toots!
先生  打扰下
Excuse me, sir!
这位小姐用我的硬币玩  这是我赢的钱
This lady played my quarter, this is my money.
小姐  真的是这样吗
Is that true miss?
卖毒品给小孩
Sells drugs to kids.
什么
What?!
她卖毒品给小孩
She sells drugs to kids.
那是我的硬币
It was my quarter!
那硬币是她的吗
Was it her quarter?
我们等吃晚餐时再聊如何
How about we talk about this over dinner?
好了  小姐  请你出去
Okay lady, you're out of here.
不  你不能逮捕我
No! No, you can't arrest me!
我才不要重回火坑
No!! I won't go back! I won't go back to that hell hole!!
-我只是要把你带出去而已  -好的
- I'm just taking you outside! - Oh, okay.
快点  得凑齐四样东西
Okay, come on, I can't get married until I get something old,
旧的新的借的蓝的  我们才能结婚
something new, something borrowed, and something blue.
这是蓝色的  而且也是新的
Okay, here's something, here's something blue and new.
你真有效率  我爱你
You're so efficient. I love you!
走吧
Let's go!
还不行  我们还需要旧的东西
No-no-no! We need something old!
我皮夹里有个保险套  从我十二岁放到现在
Okay, I have a condom in my wallet I've had since I was twelve.
这个有用啊
That'll work!
我想应该不能用了
I don't think so.
好  现在只剩借来的东西
Okay, now we just need something borrowed!
那就把这个拿走
Here just...take this.
这是偷窃
That's stealing!
到时再还回来就是了  塞进你的裙子里
No, we'll-we'll bring it back! Just put it under your dress.
好啦  先结了婚再说
Okay, one thing at a time.
你要玩吗
Are you gonna play?
不要  我没半毛钱
No-no, I don't really have any money.
只是时候未到而已
Not yet, anyway...
你不玩就不能坐在这里
You can't sit here if you're not gonna play.
你好  我是莉贾纳·费兰吉
Hello. My name is Regina Phalange.
我是生意人  这趟是来出差的
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
你要我的名片吗
Would you like to see my card?
我的名片夹到哪儿去了
Ooh, what did I do with my file-a-facts?
一定是忘在B会议室了
I must've left it in conference room B.
14点
14.
再加
Hit me!
天啊  请容我说句
Oh my God! May I just say
两位先生的手一模一样哦
that you two gentlemen have the exact same hands!
一个模子刻出来的
They're identical!
我在商界这么久  从来没看过这种事
Now, I've never seen anything like that in the business world.
别再说了
Stop it!
费兰吉女士  你是局外人
Uhh, Ms. Phalange, may I ask you a question
我能请教你一个问题吗
as an impartial person at-at this table?
请你别再说了
Please stop it!
你愿不愿意花大钱  在娱乐场所
Wouldn't you pay good money to see these identical hands
看这样完全一样的手的表演呢
showcased in some type of a uh, entertainment venue?
只要你愿意离开  我就把手砍下来送你
If you leave now, I will chop off my hand and give it too you!
我不是刚把你赶出去了吗
Didn't I just throw you out of here?
不  你赶出去的是菲比
No, you threw out Phoebe.
我是莉贾纳·费兰吉  费兰吉
I'm Regina Phalange. Phalange!
小姐  你别闹了
Come on, lady!
请你把他也带走
Please, please take him too.
-我  别这样嘛  -走吧
- Me?! Oh come on, man! - Come on.
你不能这样  我是你的双胞手耶
You can't do this! Come on!  I'm your hand twin!!
你好  请来个婚礼
Hello! One marriage please!
对  我们要结婚
Yep, we wanna get married!
有婚礼正在进行  先请坐
Well, there's a service in progress. Have a seat.
好吧
All right.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
这是结婚进行曲  听了有没有吓到
Oh, that's The Wedding March. Does, does that freak you out?
没有  因为那是毕业歌
No, only because that's the graduation song.
好了  来吧  我们要结婚了
Okay!  This is it!  We're gonna get married!
你确定你真的想结婚吗
Are you sure you wanna do this?
你好  罗斯太太
Well, hello, Mrs. Ross!
你好  瑞秋先生
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel!
等等  好
Wait! Okay!